getplan.co 2017-05-13

# Plan Privacy Policy

Plan Privacy Policy
Last Updated: 10 January, 2016
This policy describes how Plan (“Plan,” “we,” and “us”) may use and disclose
information we collect from users (“you”), and your choices about such uses and
disclosures. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our
application (“service”), visiting our website at www.getplan.co, or transacting business
with us. By using our website or application, you are accepting the practices described
herein.
    1. User Information Collection
           o   We may collect information that can identify you such as your name and
               email address ("personal information") and other information that does not
               identify you. We may collect this information through a website or a
               mobile application. By using the service, you are authorizing us to gather,
               parse and retain data related to the provision of the service.
                   §   Information you provide. In order to register as a user with Plan,
                       you will be asked to sign in using your Google account. If you do
                       so, you authorize us to access certain account information,
                       including, but not limited to, Calendar and Contacts data.
           o   Use of technologies to collect information. We use various technologies to
               collect information from your device and about your activities on our
               service.
                   §   Information collected automatically. We automatically collect
                       information from your browser or device when you access and use
                       our service. This information could include your IP address, device
                       ID and type, your browser type and language, the operating system
                       used by your device, access times, your mobile device’s

  geographic location while our application is actively running, and
  the referring website address.
§ Cookies and Use of Cookie Data. When you visit our service, we
  may assign your device one or more cookies to facilitate access to
  our service and to personalize your experience. Through the use of
  a cookie, we also may automatically collect information about your
  activity on our service, such as the pages you visit, the time and
  date of your visits and the links you click. If we advertise, we (or
  third parties) may use certain data collected on our service to show
  you Plan advertisements on other sites or applications.
§ Other Technologies. We may use standard Internet technology,
  such as web beacons and other similar technologies, to track your
  use of our service and to deliver or communicate with cookies. We
  also may include web beacons in advertisements or email
  messages to determine whether messages have been opened and
  acted upon. The information we obtain in this manner enables us to
  customize the services we offer users, to deliver targeted
  advertisements and to measure the overall effectiveness of our
  online advertising, content, programming or other activities.
§ Information collected by third parties for advertising
  purposes. We may allow service providers, advertising companies
  and ad networks, and other third parties to display advertisements
  on our service. These companies may use tracking technologies,
  such as cookies or web beacons, to collect information about users
  who view or interact with their advertisements. We provide
  personal information in a non-identifying manner to third parties.
  Some of these third-party advertising companies may be
  advertising networks that are members of the Network Advertising

                Initiative, which offers a single location to opt out of ad targeting
                from member companies (www.networkadvertising.org). Opting
                out will not decrease the number of advertisements you see.
2. How we use collected information
     o  We may use information that we collect about you to:
            §   deliver and improve our products and services, and manage our
                business;
            §   manage your account and provide you with customer support;
            §   perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our
                or others’ products, services, or content;
            §   communicate with you by email, postal mail, telephone and/or
                mobile devices about products or services that may be of interest to
                you either from us or other third parties;
            §   develop, display, and track content and advertising tailored to your
                interests on our service and other sites, including providing our
                advertisements to you when you visit other sites;
            §   website or mobile application analytics;
            §   verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with
                contests and sweepstakes;
            §   enforce or exercise any rights in our Terms of Use; and
            §   perform functions or services as otherwise described to you at the
                time of collection.
     o  Job applicants. If your personal information is submitted through our
        website when applying for a position with our company, the information
        will be used solely in connection with considering and acting upon your

         application. We may retain your personal information, but only for the
         purpose of considering your application for current or future available
         positions. This information, which may include your name and contact
         information, prior education and experience, and other information you
         provide to us, may be shared with third-party service providers retained by
         us to collect, maintain and analyze candidate submissions for job postings.
         In all circumstances, we may perform these functions directly or use a
         third party vendor to perform these functions on our behalf who will be
         obligated to use your personal information only to perform services for us.
         Also, if you access our service from a third party social platform, such as
         Facebook, we may share non-personal information with that platform to
         the extent permitted by your agreement with it and its privacy settings.
3. With whom we share your information
      o  Personal information. We do not share your personal information with
         others except as indicated in this Privacy Policy or when we inform you
         and give you an opportunity to opt out of having your personal
         information shared. We may share personal information with:
             §    Service providers: We may share information, including personal
                  and financial information, with third parties that perform certain
                  services on our behalf. These services may include fulfilling
                  orders, providing customer service and marketing assistance,
                  performing business and sales analysis, ad tracking and analytics,
                  member screenings, supporting our service functionality, and
                  supporting contests, sweepstakes, surveys and other features
                  offered through our service. These service providers may have
                  access to personal information needed to perform their functions
                  but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other
                  purposes.

      §   Other Situations. We may disclose your information, including
          personal information:
              §  In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand,
                 a court order, or a request for cooperation from a law
                 enforcement or other government agency; to establish or
                 exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or
                 as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise
                 or waive any legal objection or right available to us.
              §  When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection
                 with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action
                 regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other
                 wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or
                 safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others;
                 to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law
                 enforcement; or to enforce our Terms of Use or other
                 agreements or policies.
              §  In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such
                 as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger,
                 consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of
                 bankruptcy.
o Aggregated and/or non-personal information. We may use and share non-
  personal information we collect under any of the above circumstances. We
  may also share it with third parties to develop and deliver targeted
  advertising on our service and on websites or applications of third parties,
  and to analyze and report on advertising you see. We may combine non-
  personal information we collect with additional non- personal information
  collected from other sources. We also may share aggregated, non-personal

          information, or personal information in hashed, non-human readable form,
          with third parties, including advisors, advertisers and investors, for the
          purpose of conducting general business analysis or other business
          purposes. For example, we may engage a data provider who may collect
          web log data from you (including IP address and information about your
          browser or operating system), or place or recognize a unique cookie on
          your browser to enable you to receive customized ads or content. The
          cookies may reflect de-identified demographic or other data linked to data
          you voluntarily have submitted to us (such as your email address), that we
          may share with a data provider solely in hashed, non-human readable
          form. To opt-out of cookies that may be set by third party data or
          advertising partners, please go to http:// www.aboutads.info/choices/.
4. Your choices about collection and use of your information
      o   You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but that may
          result in you being unable to use certain features of our service because
          such information may be required in order for you to register as user;
          purchase products or services; participate in a contest, promotion, survey,
          or sweepstakes; ask a question; or initiate other transactions.
      o   Our service may also deliver notifications to your phone or mobile device.
          You can disable these notifications by deleting the relevant service or by
          changing the settings on your mobile device.
      o   You can also control information collected by cookies. You can delete or
          decline cookies by changing your browser settings. Click “help” in the
          toolbar of most browsers for instructions.
5. How we protect your personal information
   We take security measures to help safeguard your personal information from
   unauthorized access and disclosure. However, no system can be completely

   secure. Therefore, although we take steps to secure your information, we do not
   promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information, chats, or
   other communications will always remain secure. Users should also take care with
   how they handle and disclose their personal information and should avoid sending
   personal information through insecure email. Please refer to the Federal Trade
   Commission's website at http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/menus/consumer/data.shtm for
   information about how to protect yourself against identity theft.
6. Information you provide about yourself while using our service
   We provide areas on our service where you can post information about yourself
   and others and communicate with others. Such postings are governed by our
   Terms of Use. Also, whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information on
   publicly-viewable pages, that information will be publicly available and can be
   collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you
   may receive unsolicited messages. We cannot control who reads your posting or
   what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we
   encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal
   information.
7. Children's privacy
   Although our service is a general audience service, we restrict the use of our
   service to individuals age 13 and above. We do not knowingly collect, maintain,
   or use personal information from children under the age of 13.
8. Visiting our service from outside the United States
   If you are visiting our service from outside the United States, please be aware that
   your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States
   and globally where our servers are located and our central database is operated.
   By using our services, you understand and agree that your information may be

    transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as
    described in this privacy policy.
9. No Rights of Third Parties
    This Privacy Policy does not create rights enforceable by third parties or require
    disclosure of any personal information relating to users of the website.
10. Changes to this Privacy Policy
    We will sometimes update this Privacy Policy. When we post changes to this
    Privacy Policy, we will revise the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy
    Policy. We recommend that you check our service from time to time to inform
    yourself of any changes in this Privacy Policy or any of our other policies.
11. How to contact us
    If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at
    hello@getplan.co with the subject line “Privacy Policy.”
